Inventory of the Candle in the wind: motion picture film
Hoover Institution Archives
Candle in the wind: motion picture film
1984.
88008
1 item (32 motion picture film reels, 29 boxes of film) (6.1 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Relates to various religious communities within the Soviet Union, and to the relationship between church and state in the Soviet Union. Includes raw footage, outtakes, and original source footage.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1988.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
Relates to various religious communities within the Soviet Union, and to the relationship between church and state in the Soviet Union. Includes raw footage, outtakes, and original source footage.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Soviet Union--Religion--Pictorial works.; Motion pictures
Collection Contents
- "Baptisten," 16mm, 400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
  For information on a use copy, please contact Hoover Institution Archives
- "Candle in the Wind Sound," 16mm, 1500ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "Lenin I and II," 2 reels, 16mm, 1800, 1950ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "Lenin III," 16mm, unknown legnthft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "Part 1 The Russian Orthodox Church," 16mm, 1100ft., 1968 (Box film shelf)
- "Part 2 The Russian Orthodox Church," 16mm, 1100ft., 1968 (Box film shelf)
- "Past and Present II," 16mm, 1200ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "Workprint," 2 reels, 16mm, 1000, 1100ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 00-05," 8 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 200-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 16-17," 6 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 340-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 17-19," 6 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 300-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 19-21," 11 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 70-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 21-28," 11 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 75-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 28-31," 8 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 340-425ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 32-33," 8 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 5-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 34-36," 8 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 155-460ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 36-41," 13 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 100-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 41-47," 8 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 190-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 4-15," 7 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 280-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 41-56," 11 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 50-500ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 47-55," 9 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 75-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 56-57," 10 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 20-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 57-58," 10 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 40-430ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 59-64," 10 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 40-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 64-72," 8 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 100-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 72-80," 8 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 50-410ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 81-83," 6 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 380-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 91-94," 6 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 385-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 95-99," 9 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 110-400ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- "16mm Neg. 99-Misc. Rolls," 12 reels, 16mm, lengths ranging from 25-950ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 33, 60 reels, lengths ranging from 5-310 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 34, 37 reels, lengths ranging from 10-600 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 35, 61 reels, lengths ranging from 5-440 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 36, 71 reels, lengths ranging from 1 foot to 145 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 37, 61 reels, lengths ranging from 5-250 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 38, 18 reels, lengths ranging from 75-650 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 39, 48 reels, lengths ranging from 5-550 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 40, 35 reels, lengths ranging from 5-350 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 41, 27 reels, lengths ranging from 10-525 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 42, 28 reels, lengths ranging from 10-525 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 43, 24 reels, lengths ranging from 20-800 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 44, 36 reels, lengths ranging from 20-500 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 45, 49 reels, lengths ranging from 10-350 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 46, 22 reels, lengths ranging from 20-540 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 47, 10 reels, lengths ranging from 50-1100 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reel, box 48, undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 50, 143 reels in 6 boxes, lengths ranging from 25-100 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 51, 142 reels in 6 boxes, lengths ranging from 5-100 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 52, 162 reels in 6 boxes, lengths ranging from 5-150 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 53, 141 reels in 6 boxes, lengths ranging from 5-150 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 54, 91 reels in 7 boxes, lengths ranging from 15-1000 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 55, 115 reels in 6 boxes, lengths ranging from 5-250 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 56, 143 reels in 7 boxes, lengths ranging from 5-900 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 57, 138 reels in 6 boxes, lengths ranging from 5-175 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reels, box 58, 93 reels in 9 boxes, lengths ranging from 5-1000 ft., undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reel, box 59, undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reel, box 60, undated (Box film shelf)
- Untitled reel, box 61, undated (Box film shelf)